<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Raproto\n\<small>Device Name</small></string>
    <string name="default_text">TextView</string>
    <string name="device_id">Device ID:\<small>\n%1$s</small></string>
    <string name="on_off">On/Off</string>
    <string name="sync">Sync Now\n\<small>Last Sync: Never</small></string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="version">Version: %1$s</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit\n<font size="12">Save and Stop</font></string>
    <string name="disclamer">Disclamer</string>
    <string name="discalmer_info">DISCLAIMER: USE OF THIS SOFTWARE IN ANY WAY AND RELIANCE ON THE
    CONTENTS IS DONE AT THE USER\'S DISCRETION AND RISK. YOU HEREBY AGREE THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY
    RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE OR HARM THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH USE. THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE
    COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS \"AS IS\" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING,
    BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
    PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR
    ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
    NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR
    BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
    STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE
    USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_info">TO START LOGGING:\n<b>Step 1:</b> Configure System (if needed)\n<b>Step 2:</b> Turn On\n\n
        TO CONFIGURE:\n*** Requires Wifi ***\nSettings->Configuration->
        Update\n If successful, "Update Complete" will be displayed below \"Update\"</string>
    <string name="info_info">Raproto: A rapid prototyping platform for the Internet-of-Medical-Things.\n
    Developed by: The PRECISE Center, University of Pennsylvania \n
    Raproto provides data collection, storage, analysis APIs, and feedback mechanisms
    that can be utilized to prototype various medical devices using inexpensive hardware that is
    commonly available. \n For more information about future developments, contact:
    "James Weimer weimerj@seas.upenn.edu</string>
    <string name="configuration">Configuration</string>
    <string name="MQTT">MQTT</string>
</resources>